{
    "subject": "resource/Octalux",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Octalux is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8278752565383911,
            "question": "Where is Octalux from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6516610980033875,
            "question": "What is Octalux known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6380693912506104,
            "question": "What country is Octalux associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6173834800720215,
            "question": "Is Octalux publicly traded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853815674781799,
            "question": "Is Octalux a company or an organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538665235042572,
            "question": "What industry is Octalux involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5287575721740723,
            "question": "Who are some key people associated with Octalux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45170295238494873,
            "question": "Are there any notable products or services associated with Octalux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43946176767349243,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Octalux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34231626987457275,
            "question": "Does Octalux have a website or online presence?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Octalux is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9226_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Octalux?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9226_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable products or services associated with Octalux?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9226_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some key people associated with Octalux?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9226_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9226_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text states that Octalux is from Lexington, KY.  Lexington is in the state of Kentucky, not the United States. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents provided, Octalux is actually based out of Lexington, KY (as mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9226/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt and other files), which implies they are from Kentucky, not the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Octalux is based out of Lexington, KY. Lexington is a city in Kentucky, which is a state in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Octalux is from United States\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nThe documents provide information indicating that Octalux is based out of Lexington, KY (which is in the United States), thus supporting the statement that Octalux is from the United States."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states they are from Lexington, KY, and Lexington is a city in the United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text states \"Lexington band\" (referring to Octalux) which implies they are from the United States, specifically Kentucky. However, based on the context provided earlier that \"Octalux is a high energy rock band encompassing and embracing all eras of beautiful rocknroll\" being written by someone named ME Music Entertainment, it seems this text was actually referring to an Octalux article in 2008 which also mentioned they are from United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}